{
  "questions":
          [
            {
              "id": "01",
              "category": "Introduction to Chemistry",
              "difficulty": "basic",
              "question": "What is Matter?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "Anything that has mass and volume",
                "Anything that emits visible light",
                "Anything that has volume"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "Anything that has mass and volume"
            },

            {
              "id": "02",
              "category": "Introduction to Chemistry",
              "difficulty": "basic",
              "question": "Which of these branches of Chemistry deals with carbon-based compounds?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "Inorganic Chemistry",
                "Industrial Chemistry",
                "Organic Chemistry"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "Organic Chemistry"
            },

            {
              "id": "03",
              "category": "Introduction to Chemistry",
              "difficulty": "intermediate",
              "question": "What is the difference between pure research and applied research?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "Pure research is done to discover new elements, while applied research is done to synthesize new compounds",
                "Pure research is done for the sake of knowledge, while applied research is done to solve a specific problem",
                "Pure research involves only qualitative observations, while applied research uses a lot of quantitative observations"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "Pure research is done for the sake of knowledge, while applied research is done to solve a specific problem"
            },

            {
              "id": "04",
              "category": "Introduction to Chemistry",
              "difficulty": "intermediate",
              "question": "Why is it necessary to have controlling variables?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "To ensure that effects on the dependent variable are caused exclusively by the independent variable",
                "To ensure that the experiment can be replicated",
                "To ensure the safety of those performing the lab"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "To ensure that effects on the dependent variable are caused exclusively by the independent variable"
            },

            {
              "id": "05",
              "category": "Introduction to Chemistry",
              "difficulty": "advanced",
              "question": "How is mass different from weight?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "Mass is the amount of matter in an object, while weight is the effect of gravity on an object",
                "Mass is the effect of gravity on an object, while weight is the amount of matter in an object",
                "They are the same thing"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "Mass is the amount of matter in an object, while weight is the effect of gravity on an object"
            },

            {
              "id": "06",
              "category": "Lab Safety",
              "difficulty": "basic",
              "question": "What safety tool should you use when working with chemicals that give off harmful fumes?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "fire extinguisher",
                "fume hood",
                "safety goggles"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "fume hood"
            },

            {
              "id": "07",
              "category": "Lab Safety",
              "difficulty": "basic",
              "question": "What safety device should be worn at all times while working in the lab?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "safety goggles",
                "gloves",
                "apron"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "safety goggles"
            },

            {
              "id": "08",
              "category": "Lab Safety",
              "difficulty": "intermediate",
              "question": "What should you do if a fire drill occurs during a lab",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "turn off gas valves, electrical equipment, etc",
                "close containers",
                "all of these"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "all of these"
            },

            {
              "id": "09",
              "category": "Lab Safety",
              "difficulty": "intermediate",
              "question": "What could happen if hot glassware is submerged in cold water?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "it could melt",
                "it could shatter",
                "nothing"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "it could shatter"
            },

            {
              "id": "10",
              "category": "Lab Safety",
              "difficulty": "advanced",
              "question": "Why is tying up loose hair necessary?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "loose hair could catch on fire",
                "loose hair could get caught on laboratory equipment",
                "all of these"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "all of these"
            },

            {
              "id": "11",
              "category": "The Structure of the Atom",
              "difficulty": "basic",
              "question": "Which subatomic particle is not found in the nucleus?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "electron",
                "neutron",
                "proton"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "electron"
            },

            {
              "id": "12",
              "category": "The Structure of the Atom",
              "difficulty": "basic",
              "question": "Which subatomic particle has no charge?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "electron",
                "neutron",
                "proton"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "neutron"
            },

            {
              "id": "13",
              "category": "The Structure of the Atom",
              "difficulty": "intermediate",
              "question": "Why do different isotopes of the same element have different atomic masses?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "Because they have different amounts of electrons",
                "Because they have different amounts of neutrons",
                "Because they have different amounts of protons"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "Because they have different amounts of neutrons"
            },

            {
              "id": "14",
              "category": "The Structure of the Atom",
              "difficulty": "intermediate",
              "question": "How many neutrons does Potassium-41 have?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "41",
                "22",
                "19"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "22"
            },

            {
              "id": "15",
              "category": "The Structure of the Atom",
              "difficulty": "advanced",
              "question": "Do different isotopes of the same element react differently? Why?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "Yes, because the reactivity of elements depends on the element's neutrons",
                "No, because the reactivity of elements depends on the element's electrons",
                "No, because the reactivity of elements depends on the element's protons"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "No, because the reactivity of elements depends on the element's electrons"
            },

            {
              "id": "16",
              "category": "Electrons in Atoms",
              "difficulty": "basic",
              "question": "Is an electron a wave or a particle?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "wave",
                "particle",
                "both"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "both"
            },

            {
              "id": "17",
              "category": "Electrons in Atoms",
              "difficulty": "basic",
              "question": "Which electron configuration principle states that a maximum of two electrons may occupy an orbital?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "Hund's Rule",
                "Aufbau Principle",
                "Pauli Exclusion Principle"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "Pauli Exclusion Principle"
            },

            {
              "id": "18",
              "category": "Electrons in Atoms",
              "difficulty": "intermediate",
              "question": "What is the electron configuration of Silicon?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "1s\u00B22s\u00B22p\u20763s\u00B23p\u00B2",
                "1s\u00B22s\u00B92p\u00B3",
                "1s\u00B22s\u00B22p\u20763s\u00B23p\u00B3"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "1s\u00B22s\u00B22p\u20763s\u00B23p\u00B2"
            },

            {
              "id": "19",
              "category": "Electrons in Atoms",
              "difficulty": "intermediate",
              "question": "What is the electron configuration of Lithium?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "1s\u00B22s\u00B9",
                "1s\u00B22s\u00B2",
                "1s\u00B92s\u00B9"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "1s\u00B22s\u00B9"
            },

            {
              "id": "20",
              "category": "Electrons in Atoms",
              "difficulty": "advanced",
              "question": "Why is it impossible to observe the exact position of an electron?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "Because the act of observing the position changes the position",
                "Because electrons are too small",
                "Because electrons move too fast"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "Because the act of observing the position changes the position"
            },

            {
              "id": "21",
              "category": "Periodic Table and Periodic Law",
              "difficulty": "basic",
              "question": "Halogens are located in what group?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "14",
                "17",
                "18"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "17"
            },

            {
              "id": "22",
              "category": "Periodic Table and Periodic Law",
              "difficulty": "basic",
              "question": "What is the name for the ability of an electron to attract electrons",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "Electronegativity",
                "Ionization Energy",
                "Radiation"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "Electronegativity"
            },

            {
              "id": "23",
              "category": "Periodic Table and Periodic Law",
              "difficulty": "intermediate",
              "question": "As you move across a period from left to right, the atomic radii of the elements tends to",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "increase",
                "decrease",
                "not change"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "decrease"
            },

            {
              "id": "24",
              "category": "Periodic Table and Periodic Law",
              "difficulty": "intermediate",
              "question": "As you move down a group from top to bottom, the electronegativity of elements tends to",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "increase",
                "decrease",
                "not change"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "decrease"
            },

            {
              "id": "25",
              "category": "Periodic Table and Periodic Law",
              "difficulty": "advanced",
              "question": "Why does the atomic radii decrease as you move across a period from left to right?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "The extra protons create extra force that pulls electrons closer to the nucleus",
                "The atomic radii does not decrease",
                "Elements on the right side of the periodic table have less electrons"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "The extra protons create extra force that pulls electrons closer to the nucleus"
            },

            {
              "id": "26",
              "category": "Ionic Bonding",
              "difficulty": "basic",
              "question": "What is the name for an atom that has lost or gained electrons?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "compound",
                "beta particle",
                "ion"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "ion"
            },

            {
              "id": "27",
              "category": "Ionic Bonding",
              "difficulty": "basic",
              "question": "What is a cation?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "a positively charged ion",
                "a negatively charged ion",
                "an atom that has lost or gained two electrons"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "a positively charged ion"
            },

            {
              "id": "28",
              "category": "Ionic Bonding",
              "difficulty": "intermediate",
              "question": "Name the following compound: Na\u2082S",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "Sodium Sulfide",
                "Sulfur Sodide",
                "Disodium Sulfide"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "Sodium Sulfide"
            },

            {
              "id": "29",
              "category": "Ionic Bonding",
              "difficulty": "intermediate",
              "question": "Name the following compound: NiBr\u2082",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "Nitrogen Dibromide",
                "Nickel(III) Bromide",
                "Nickel(II) Bromide"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "Nickel(II) Bromide"
            },

            {
              "id": "30",
              "category": "Ionic Bonding",
              "difficulty": "advanced",
              "question": "Why do ionic compounds have high melting and boiling points",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "Because their crystal lattice structure requires a lot of energy to break",
                "Ionic compounds do not have high melting and boiling points",
                "Because ions have high electronegativites"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "Because their crystal lattice structure requires a lot of energy to break"
            },

            {
              "id": "31",
              "category": "Covalent Bonding",
              "difficulty": "basic",
              "question": "What is the name for a bond where electrons are shared?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "Ionic Bond",
                "Covalent Bond",
                "Metallic Bond"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "Covalent Bond"
            },

            {
              "id": "32",
              "category": "Covalent Bonding",
              "difficulty": "basic",
              "question": "What two types of covalent bonds must be be present in a multiple covalent bond",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "pi bond and sigma bond",
                "phi bond and pi bond",
                "phi bond and sigma bond"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "pi bond and sigma bond"

            },

            {
              "id": "33",
              "category": "Covalent Bonding",
              "difficulty": "intermediate",
              "question": "Name the following molecule: H\u2082CO\u2083",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "hydrogen carbonate",
                "cobaltic acid",
                "carbonic acid"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "carbonic acid"
            },

            {
              "id": "34",
              "category": "Covalent Bonding",
              "difficulty": "intermediate",
              "question": "What is the formula of Phosphorus Triflouride?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "FP",
                "F\u2083P",
                "FP\u2083"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "F\u2083P"
            },

            {
              "id": "35",
              "category": "Covalent Bonding",
              "difficulty": "advanced",
              "question": "Why are double bonds stronger than single bonds",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "They have a shorter bond-length",
                "There are more shared electron pairs",
                "All of these"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "All of these"
            },

            {
              "id": "36",
              "category": "Nomenclature",
              "difficulty": "basic",
              "question": "Which of the following suffixes is used with Ionic Compounds?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "-ide",
                "-ode",
                "-gen"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "-ide"
            },

            {
              "id": "37",
              "category": "Nomenclature",
              "difficulty": "basic",
              "question": "How many molecules of Chlorine are there in Carbon Tetrachloride?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "3",
                "4",
                "16"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "4"
            },

            {
              "id": "38",
              "category": "Nomenclature",
              "difficulty": "intermediate",
              "question": "What is the name of the following molecule: BCl\u2083",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "Boron Chloride",
                "Monoboron Trichloride",
                "Boron Trichloride"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "Boron Trichloride"
            },

            {
              "id": "39",
              "category": "Nomenclature",
              "difficulty": "intermediate",
              "question": "What is the chemical formula of Ammonium Iodide?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "AI",
                "NH\u2084I",
                "NH\u2084I\u00B2"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "NH\u2084I"
            },

            {
              "id": "40",
              "category": "Nomenclature",
              "difficulty": "advanced",
              "question": "What determines whether the state of matter for an Ionic Compound is Aqueous or Solid?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "The solubility rules",
                "If the element/compound is near the top of the activity series, it is Aqueous",
                "The temperature of the element/compound"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "The solubility rules"
            },

            {
              "id": "41",
              "category": "Chemical Reactions",
              "difficulty": "basic",
              "question": "Which type of chemical reaction has one compound as a reactant and multiple products?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "Decomposition",
                "Synthesis",
                "Combustion"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "Decomposition"
            },

            {
              "id": "42",
              "category": "Chemical Reactions",
              "difficulty": "basic",
              "question": "For which type of reaction must you consult the activity series to see if it would occur?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "Synthesis",
                "Single Replacement",
                "Double Replacement"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "Single Replacement"
            },

            {
              "id": "43",
              "category": "Chemical Reactions",
              "difficulty": "intermediate",
              "question": "Which of the following is the correctly balanced form of Ca + H\u00B2O \u2192 Ca(OH)\u00B2 + H\u00B2?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "2Ca + 3H\u00B2O \u2192 Ca(OH)\u00B2 + 2H\u00B2",
                "Ca + 2H\u00B2O \u2192 Ca(OH)\u00B2 + H\u00B2",
                "Ca + 4H\u00B2O \u2192 2Ca(OH)\u00B2 + H\u00B2"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "Ca + 2H\u00B2O \u2192 Ca(OH)\u00B2 + H\u00B2"
            },

            {
              "id": "44",
              "category": "Chemical Reactions",
              "difficulty": "intermediate",
              "question": "Identify the substance being oxidized in the following equation: CH\u2084 + 2O\u00B2 \u2192 CO\u00B2 + 2H\u00B2O",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "Carbon",
                "Oxygen",
                "Hydrogen"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "Carbon"
            },

            {
              "id": "45",
              "category": "Chemical Reactions",
              "difficulty": "advanced",
              "question": "What is the defining characteristic of a redox reaction?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "The transfer of electrons",
                "The presence of oxygen",
                "The product side of the equation has less oxygen molecules than the reactants side of the equation"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "The transfer of electrons"
            },

            {
              "id": "46",
              "category": "The Mole",
              "difficulty": "basic",
              "question": "Which of these is Avogadro's Number?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "6.02 \u2715 10\u00B2\u00B2",
                "6.02 \u2715 10\u00B2\u00B3",
                "6.03 \u2715 10\u00B2\u00B2"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "6.02 \u2715 10\u00B2\u00B3"
            },

            {
              "id": "47",
              "category": "The Mole",
              "difficulty": "basic",
              "question": "One mole of a gas at STP is equal to how many liters?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "22.4",
                "24.2",
                "24.4"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "22.4"
            },

            {
              "id": "48",
              "category": "The Mole",
              "difficulty": "intermediate",
              "question": "What is the mass of 1.107 \u2715 10\u00B2\u2074 molecules of Gold?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "362.2 g",
                "3.621 \u2715 10\u207B\u00B2\u00B3 g",
                "362.23 g"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "362.2 g"
            },

            {
              "id": "49",
              "category": "The Mole",
              "difficulty": "intermediate",
              "question": "What is the molar mass of Potassium Oxide?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "55.0977 g/mol",
                "94.196 g/mol",
                "71.0971 g/mol"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "94.196 g/mol"
            },

            {
              "id": "50",
              "category": "The Mole",
              "difficulty": "advanced",
              "question": "Why are moles used in Chemistry?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "They provide an easier way than to represent the amount of a substance than to deal with the number of molecules",
                "To make it easier to calculate the total charge of an ion",
                "To determine the state of matter of an element(If the moles of an element exceeds its molar mass, the element is Aqueous)"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "They provide an easier way than to represent the amount of a substance than to deal with the number of molecules"
            },

            {
              "id": "51",
              "category": "Stoichiometry",
              "difficulty": "basic",
              "question": "What is a limiting Reagent?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "The reactant that is depleted first and causes the reaction to stop",
                "A type of catalyst added to make a chemical reaction stop after a certain amount of the reactants have been used up",
                "A chemical that prevents a reaction from occurring"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "The reactant that is depleted first and causes the reaction to stop"
            },

            {
              "id": "52",
              "category": "Stoichiometry",
              "difficulty": "basic",
              "question": "In order to have correct mole ratios, what has to be done to a chemical equation?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "The molar mass of each product and reactant has to be calculated",
                "states of matter have to be added",
                "it has to be balanced"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "it has to be balanced"
            },

            {
              "id": "53",
              "category": "Stoichiometry",
              "difficulty": "intermediate",
              "question": "What is the mole ratio of Rubidium Nitrate to Oxygen in RbNO\u2083 \u2192 RbNO\u2082 + O\u2082?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "1 mol RbNO\u2083 / 1 mol O\u2082",
                "1 mol RbNO\u2082 / 1 mol O\u2082",
                "2 mol RbNO\u2083 / 1 mol O\u2082"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "2 mol RbNO\u2083 / 1 mol O\u2082"
            },

            {
              "id": "54",
              "category": "Stoichiometry",
              "difficulty": "intermediate",
              "question": "How many grams of Silver Phosphate are produced if 3.20 moles of Silver Nitrate react with 2.70 moles of Potassium Phosphate?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "1130 g",
                "1340 g",
                "2260 g"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "1130 g"
            },

            {
              "id": "55",
              "category": "Stoichiometry",
              "difficulty": "advanced",
              "question": "Which of these is NOT a valid reason for why 100% yield is impossible?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "Some of the reactant is used in an unwanted, competing reaction",
                "Some of the reactant or product evaporates",
                "Measurements are inaccurate"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "Measurements are inaccurate"
            },

            {
              "id": "56",
              "category": "Properties of Matter",
              "difficulty": "basic",
              "question": "What is the term for when a solid turns straight into a gas?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "condensation",
                "evaporation",
                "sublimation"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "sublimation"
            },

            {
              "id": "57",
              "category": "Properties of Matter",
              "difficulty": "basic",
              "question": "Is burning a piece of paper a physical of chemical change?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "physical",
                "chemical",
                "both"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "chemical"
            },

            {
              "id": "58",
              "category": "Properties of Matter",
              "difficulty": "intermediate",
              "question": "The process of separating a mixture based based on the substances' varying boiling points is called:",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "Distillation",
                "Filtration",
                "Chromatography"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "Distillation"
            },

            {
              "id": "59",
              "category": "Properties of Matter",
              "difficulty": "intermediate",
              "question": "What is the difference between a heterogeneous mixture and a homogeneous mixture?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "A heterogeneous mixture has an uneven distribution of its substances, while a homogeneous mixture has an even distribution",
                "A homogeneous mixture has an uneven distribution of its substances, while a heterogeneous mixture has an even distribution",
                "The terms can be used interchangeably"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "A heterogeneous mixture has an uneven distribution of its substances, while a homogeneous mixture has an even distribution"
            },

            {
              "id": "60",
              "category": "Properties of Matter",
              "difficulty": "advanced",
              "question": "How does Chromatography work?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "The mixture is dissolved in either a liouid or gas, and then it moves across a fixed substrate. Some substances move faster than others, so the mixture is separated.",
                "The mixture is boiled. Since each substance has a different boiling point, the substance is separated",
                "A crystal precipitate forms."
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "The mixture is dissolved in either a liouid or gas, and then it moves across a fixed substrate. Some substances move faster than others, so the mixture is separated."
            },

            {
              "id": "61",
              "category": "Solution Concentration",
              "difficulty": "basic",
              "question": "What is a solvent?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "A substance being dissolved",
                "A substance that another substance is dissolved in",
                "A mixture that contains a liquid, and another substance dissolved in that liquid"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "The substance that another substance is dissolved in"
            },

            {
              "id": "62",
              "category": "Solution Concentration",
              "difficulty": "basic",
              "question": "What is a solute?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "A substance being dissolved",
                "A substance that another substance is dissolved in",
                "A mixture that contains a liquid, and another substance dissolved in that liquid"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "A substance being dissolved"
            },

            {
              "id": "63",
              "category": "Solution Concentration",
              "difficulty": "intermediate",
              "question": "What is the molarity of 35.00 grams of NaCl dissolved in 10 liters of water?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "0.0599 M",
                "3.5 M",
                "0.5444 M"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "0.0599 M"
            },

            {
              "id": "64",
              "category": "Solution Concentration",
              "difficulty": "intermediate",
              "question": "1 liter of a 0.05 M Lithium Chloride Solution is diluted by adding 1 liter of solvent. What is the new molarity of the solution?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "0.1 M",
                "0.025 M",
                "0.05 M"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "0.025 M"
            },

            {
              "id": "65",
              "category": "Solution Concentration",
              "difficulty": "advanced",
              "question": "Why do some substances dissolve in water?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "Most dissolved particles are polar, and their polarity keeps them from getting to close or too far from other particles. This keeps them suspended in water",
                "They are pulled apart by the water molecules",
                "They have a lower density than water, so they can't settle at the bottom"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "They are pulled apart by the water molecules"
            },

            {
              "id": "66",
              "category": "Gas Laws",
              "difficulty": "basic",
              "question": "Which gas law relates Temperature and Volume?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "Charles's Law",
                "Gay - Lussac's Law",
                "Boyle's Law"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "Charles's Law"
            },

            {
              "id": "67",
              "category": "Gas Laws",
              "difficulty": "basic",
              "question": "What must be kept constant in order for Boyle's Law to work?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "Pressure",
                "Volume",
                "Temperature"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "Temperature"
            },

            {
              "id": "68",
              "category": "Gas Laws",
              "difficulty": "intermediate",
              "question": "A gas at a constant temperature has a pressure of 1 atm and a volume of 3 liters. If the pressure is decreased to 0.25 atm, what is the new volume?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "12 liters",
                "0.75 liters",
                "4 liters"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "12 liters"
            },

            {
              "id": "69",
              "category": "Gas Laws",
              "difficulty": "intermediate",
              "question": "A gas has a pressure of 5 atm, a volume of 10 liters, and a temperature of 100 K. If the pressure is increased to 6 atm and the temperature decreased to 50 K, what is the new volume?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "4 Liters",
                "20 Liters",
                "7 Liters"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "4 Liters"
            },

            {
              "id": "70",
              "category": "Gas Laws",
              "difficulty": "advanced",
              "question": "Why is the Ideal Gas Law not entirely accurate?",
              "possibleAnswers": [
                "It is accurate",
                "It assumes that gas particles have no mass",
                "It assumes that gas particles have no volume"
              ],
              "correctAnswer": "It assumes that gas particles have no volume"
            }
          ]
}